classifieds777.com 2010-11-23

# England - Free Classifieds

This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for **CLASSIFIEDS777.COM**.  
**CLASSIFIEDS777.COM** will never use your personal data for commercial use. We will only use your personal data to facilitate the contact between our users.

LOG DATA  
When you visit **CLASSIFIEDS777.COM** , our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website ("Log Data" ). This Log Data may include information such as your IP address, browser type or the domain from which you are visiting, the web-pages you visit, the search terms you use, and any advertisements on which you click. For most users accessing the Internet from an Internet service provider the IP address will be different every time you log on. We use Log Data to monitor the use of the Site and of our Service, and for the Site's technical administration. We do not associate your IP address with any other personally identifiable information to identify you personally, except in case of violation of the Terms of Service.

COOKIES  
Like many websites, we also use "cookie" technology to collect additional website usage data and to improve the our service. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer's hard disk. We do not use cookies to collect personally identifiable information. A session cookie enables certain features of our service and is deleted from your computer when you disconnect from or leave the site. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser and may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the site. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser help file directions. Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies. You can instruct your browser, by editing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from **CLASSIFIEDS777.COM**.

LINKS  
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that **CLASSIFIEDS777.COM** is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by **CLASSIFIEDS777.COM**.  
Unless otherwise stated, **CLASSIFIEDS777.COM** is in no way related to these sites.

SITE AND SERVICE UPDATES  
We will send the user site and service announcement updates. Members are not able to un-subscribe from service announcements, which contain important information about the service. We communicate with the user to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to the account via e-mail.

NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Home page and use our best efforts to announce via e-mail so all users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will make a reasonable effort to notify users by way of an e-mail. Users have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.
